DAWID FLORIAN

NET DEVELOPER



CONTACT

532 645 060



dawidflorian99@gmail.com



In linkedin.com/in/florian-dawid



dawidflorian.pl



github.com/git-df

EDUCATION

ENGINEER.

COMPUTER SCIENCE Politechnika Rzeszowska 2019 — 2023

TECHNICIAN,

COMPUTER SCIENCE Zespół Szkół Elektrycznych i Ogólnokształcących w Krośnie

SKILLS

|.NET Core | C#

REST API

Microservices | Worker

Razor pages | Blazor | MVC

MS SQL | PostgreSQL

RabbitMQ | ASB | Masstransit

GIT

Fast Endpoints

Ling | EF Core

MediatR | CQRS

Mapper

Identity

Unit/Integration tests

XUnit | NUnit | Test container

HTML | CSS | JS

JIRA | Confluence

Slack | Zoom | Teams | Meets

SUMMARY

I am an ambitious programmer with an engineering degree. I have been working and developing at my current company for over two years, starting as a junior IT specialist. For more than a year, I have been programming in .NET technology, primarily working on APIs and microservices that form the foundation of modern applications. I am passionately developing my skills. I am a creative person who enjoys challenges and is open to new experiences.

EXPERIENCE

.NET DEVELOPER

9bits | 10/2024 — NOW

- Managing micro teams of programmers for specific functionalities.
- Being responsible for the timely completion of the micro team tasks.
- Responsibilities listed under the junior programmer position.

JUNIOR.NET DEVELOPER

9bits | 10/2023 — 10/2024

- Develop software, mainly APIs and microservices.
- Estimating tasks.
- Code review
- Documentation management.

JUNIOR IT SPECIALIST

9bits | 07/2022 — 10/2023

- Manual and regression testing of web and mobile applications.
- Analysis and resolution of problems reported by customers.
- Documentation management.

ACADEMIC INTERNSHIP

Soft Integration | 2021

- Maintaining the company's website.
- Testing solutions being implemented.

CERTIFICATES

2021 - Architecting with Google Compute Engine - Google Cloud 2019 - E12, E13, E14 - Technician IT

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.